

PROFILE.

I am a software developer and a 3rd-year computer engineering student at Çankaya University. I am interested in web development, cyber security, algorithm solving, artificial intelligence, and game development. I have participated in various game jams in the last couple of years and made video games from scratch both with teams and independently. Additionally, I have competed in Latin & standard ballroom dances for six years. Being a successful athlete requires a lot of discipline and responsibility and I believe those qualities that I have translate into my work ethic as a developer. I want to work at a company that has clear goals and a motivating vision.

EXPERIENCE ___

EKON INFORMATICS

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021 / Ankara, Turkey

INTERN - CYBER SECURITY

• During my 1-month internship at this company, I learned about cyber security fundamentals & tools and applied some basic principles.

BILICISOFT INFORMATION AND DEFENSE TECHNOLOGIES

Jul 2022 - Aug 2022 / Ankara, Turkey

INTERN - WEB DEVELOPMENT

• During my 1-month internship at this company, I developed with C and ASP.NET MVC and provided support to the projects that the company is currently working on.

EDUCATION

ÇANKAYA UNIVERSITY, ANKARA, TURKEY

2019-2024 (expected)

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Extracurricular activities

- The current president of the Çankaya University IEEE Communication Society
- The founding co-chairman of the CyberBees community (the cyber security community of Çankaya University)

SKILLS ____

PROGRAMMING SKILLS game development | Defold | Lua | C | C++

Python | ASP.NET MVC | Kali Linux | Pandas | Numpy

LANGUAGES Native: Turkish Advanced (C1): English